(Vet:)Here are a few warning
signs to look out for.
(Vet:)If you see any of them,
don't hesitate to call.
(Raj:)Thank you for taking such
good care of my little girl.
(Vet:)My pleasure.
Have a nice night.
(Leonard:)Yes, thank you for all your help.
(Penny:)Yeah. I'm sorry if you didn't think
we were taking it seriously.
(Penny:)-We love animals.
-Do you guys own any pets?
(Sheldon:)-No.
-Good.
(Howard:)I love you so much.
(Bernadette:)I love you, too.
(Amy:)-Sorry.
-Sorry.
(Man:)You guys missed
a pretty great time.
(Sheldon:)The conductor and I have
the same pocket watch.
(Man:)-It was crazy.
-Dare I say "loco?"
(Sheldon:)Oh, and, Amy, guess what?
(Sheldon:)The conductor said as
soon as he gets off work,
(Sheldon:)he can come back to the bed and
breakfast and play his banjo for us.